 

							87 Milk Street, Boston, Mass., Nov 30, 1914. 
Mrs. Theo M Davis, 

	Washington, D.C.

Dear Mrs Davis: 

The Conservators have leased from Hon W J Bryan his winter residence at Miami, Fla, known as “Villa Serena” for the 
use of Mr Davis for the four or five months next ensuing; and in the transaction Mr Bryan has expressed the wish that 
you join the Conservators in signing the lease. 

Mr Herbert Parsons of New York thinks there is no harm in your signing with us; and we wish to assure you that your so 
doing is no liability on your part and that the sole liability on account of the lease rests with Mr Davis’s Estate. 

Respectfully,

Theodore Davis Boal 
Dudley S. Dean 

Conservators for Theo M Davis   