 
National Press Bureau  
70 Fifth Avenue, New York 

AMERICAN BIOGRAPHY AND GENEALOGY 

June.10th. 1915.

Mrs.Theodore M. Davis, 

Newport, R. I. 

Dear Madam:-

Will you kindly advise us if there has ever been published a biographical sketch of 
your husband, and if so, where it may be found. We are desirous of obtaining full particular of his personal career and family history, for the National Cyclopedia of American Biography, and we will be greatly obliged if you will let us hear from you as early as possible. 

Yours very truly,

 
NATIONAL PRESS BUREAU
GEORGE DERBY, Editor. 
							