 

Villa Serena, Miami, Florida,
Haroh 16th, 1915. 

Dear Aunt Annie;- 

Just two words to tell you of you of our safe arrival here and to thank you for the telegram saying that all goes well at Edgewood. If you see Mr. Parsons, it might be well for you to explain to him that Uncle had promised you to make large provision for Pierre in his will and it was having that in mind that made you refuse to sign the Waiver of Dower until you were assured of something that could be used in this way. I also told Mr. Parsons that you knew nothing of any Trust at the time you signed the Contract and Waiver and that I, myself, only knew in a very general way that a trust arrangement was contemplated. 

I took it that Uncle suggestion to you in his letter as to the million dollars had reference to his expectation that you were going to leave this sum to Pierre and thus make up I or his neglect of the promise which he admitted to me had been made to you. I simply refresh your mind on these matters. 

I also wish to call your attention to the fact that when he wrote this letter the question of your returning the Reef the next year was left open and he was obliged to take it up the next summer, and I was called into the matter by (), or from Mrs. Newberry and later by the word from Mrs. Andrews. It was on their suggestion that I came to the Reef and took up the matter of your not returning there at all in exchange for a permanent allowance and money to provide yourself with a residence near Washington and one near Boalsburg if necessary. 

The first letter simply covered renunciation of any claim which you might have against the estate or the Reef in consideration of a large sum of money to be given to you or your heirs. Please read the over carefully with Aunt Sarah and discuss the matter with her. 

I expect to be home next Tuesday morning at 10.25 and will wire you enroute. Please take the very heat of care of yourself and believe me, every affectionately, 

Your nephew, 

P.S. It is very essential to avoid meeting any of these people until after the meeting at Mr. Parsons office a week from Thursday. If approached say I have charge of your affairs.  