
Villa Serena, Miami, Fla., 
Jan. 26th, 1915.

Mrs. Theodore M. Davis, 

Edgewood, Bethesda,  

Maryland.

Dear Aunt Annie;-

I have very nice letters from Cousin Maria and from Aunt Sarah giving me 
your news. I also have good news from Pierre and Cecile. I fancy they will be back 
about the end of next month, at least Pierre will be coming along and will come to Washington, of course to see you. Uncle is improving since Mrs. Andrews left, is 
extremely sweet and kind, but there is no marked ameloriation in his mental condition.
the improvement is merely a lessening of the severe nervous strain which had become so alarming. 

I have no plans for leaving here at present and can do nothing until some definite arrangement is made for the future. My plan, however, as far as the household here 
Is concerned, is to start everybody north in the middle of March and to gradually 
work to Newport for the last days of My, which I suppose is as early as one dares 
to go into that climate with an invalid. Please take care of yourself and if you 
do not have the time to write me, ask Aunt Sarah to write me often some of her good letters. 

Maria Cable was so delighted with her reception at Edgewood and said she quite loved your little house. In this connection, it might be well if you would send me a signed letter making  a request for the $3500. which will be needed to erect a garage sufficiently large to take care of your two machines. The present garage is only of course, a makeshift, being the porte coohere of the house. 

Affectionately, 

Your nephew 

Theodore Davis Boal  



							