 
Parsons, Closson & McIlvaine, 
52 William Street. 

New York, 
January 20, 1915.

Mrs. T. M. Davis, 
Edgewood,
Bethesda, 

Dear Mrs. Davis:

In the letter which I sent you enclosing the petition for the appointment of a guardian 
of the person of Mr. Davis I said that it was for the appointment of Terry as that guardian, but his name was omitted from the petition. Before having it sent on to be filed, I have inserted his name.

I have also had written out in typewriting the part which was in pencil. The petition now reads as follows: 

“To the Honorable the Probate Court of the City of Newport:
RESPECTFULLY represents the undersigned ANNIE B. DAVIS, of the City and County of Newport, and Sate of Rhode Island, that Theodore M. Davis, a resident of and having a legal settlement in said Newport, is a person of full age, a person of unsound mind. 

WHEREFORE your petitioner prays that Theodore D.Boal, or some other suitable person may be appointed guardian of the person of said Theodore M. Davis.”

Very Truly yours,

Herbert Parsons 



  
							