EDITORIAL DEPARTMENT 

THE NATIONAL CYCLOPEDIA OF AMERICAN BIOGRAPHY

70 Fifth Avenue, New York 

James T. WHITE & CO.
Publishers 

Jan.13th. 1916

Mrs.Theo.M.Davis, 

Newport, R. I. 

Dear Madam:-

Will you kindly advise us if there has ever been published a biographical sketch of 
your husband, and if so, where it may be found. We are desirous of obtaining full particular of his 			personal career and family history, for the National Cyclopedia of American Biography, and we will be 
greatly obliged if you will let us hear from you as early as possible. 

Yours very truly, 

	GEORGE DERBY, Editor. 
							